[Music]
[音乐]
guess we're all set up a good morning
猜我们都准备好了
from from my side welcome it's great to
从我这边欢迎
see you all I meant to say I don't
看到你我想说的我不
actually see too many of you with this
真的看到你们这个人太多了
lighting going on the the keynote has
主题演讲上的照明设备有
plenty of ambitious material for you
大量适合您的材料
today and I guess you're pretty unaware
今天，我想你还没意识到
since we didn't really reveal it up
因为我们没有真正揭露它
front my job is actually basically to
前面我的工作实际上基本上是
warm you up towards what's coming I'm
让你为即将发生的事情热身
only going to elaborate for a few
只会详细说明
minutes here before passing it on to to
分钟，然后再传递给
the rest of the crew for the in-depth
其余的船员进行了深入的研究
coverage of stuff like our socket r2 DBC
像我们的套接字r2 DBC之类的东西的覆盖范围
and cotton cover things but let's start
和棉花遮盖住东西，但让我们开始吧
with a few thoughts about the roadmap
对路线图有一些想法
and about the themes that we chose to
关于我们选择的主题
focus on not only 45 - to time frame but
不仅关注45-在时间范围内，而且
also towards 2020 we are right in the
也是到2020年，我们才是正确的
middle of the spring 5 - to spring
春季5-春季
family 5 - to milestone phase so we're
家庭5-达到里程碑阶段，所以我们
working towards the third milestone the
朝着第三个里程碑努力
RC phase the release candidates are
RC阶段发布候选对象是
going to come soon we're working towards
即将到来，我们正在努力
HD a date on July 31st and we mean to
高清日期为7月31日，我们的意思是
drop on that day I hope we actually have
希望那天我们真的有
a proper our C phase before that but
在此之前适当的我们的C相
we're really a bit time bound at this
我们真的有点时间
point and spring family 52 has lots of
点和春天家庭52有很多
things in basically in development at
基本上在开发中的东西
the moment along several themes as you
当你沿着几个主题的那一刻
might be aware we started being very
可能知道我们开始非常
theme driven in particular with the
主题尤其受
Spring Fair Mach 5 5 - the release the
Spring Fair Mach 5 5-发布
reactive theme functional API design the
反应主题功能API设计
whole Java 8 + space lining this was all
整个Java 8 +空间衬里就这些了
very theme driven embracing JDK 9 and
主题驱动的拥抱JDK 9和
now 11 for spring filmic 5 - - we had a
现在是春季电影5的11--
strong focus on startup optimizations
专注于启动优化
this is basically a a very multifaceted
这基本上是一个非常多方面的
efforts there say a
那里的努力说
a lot of knobs we can turn lots of
很多旋钮，我们可以转动很多
things we can do lots of little
我们可以做很多事的事情
optimizations we can sneak in to improve
我们可以潜入改进的优化
startup time if that is what you're
启动时间，如果那是你的时间
trying to optimize for in according to
尝试根据
your deployment scenarios that might or
您的部署方案可能或
might not matter a lot if it does matter
如果重要的话可能并不重要
then there are quite a few steps we're
那么我们有很多步骤
taking in five to two that allow you to
五到两个，让你
basically get the initial setup running
基本上使初始设置运行
more quickly than before this is ongoing
比之前进行的更快
and it's going to continue into the five
这将继续到五个
to three era for sure
到三个时代
connected to this we revisited our
与此相关的我们重新审视了我们的
annotation processing annotations are
注释处理注释是
not actually at the heart of the core
实际上不是核心的核心
container in Spring Framework in spring
Spring框架中的容器
in general but of course in terms of
一般而言，当然
everyday the everyday usage model the
每天的日常使用模型
primary usage model out there annotation
主要用法模型在那里注释
processing plays a very important role
加工起着非常重要的作用
and it comes in in many forms
它以多种形式出现
it's the annotations that we introspect
这是我们自省的注解
when you send us towards the classpath
当您将我们送往课程路径时
for finding your components in a
用于在
component scan we need to efficiently
我们需要有效地进行组件扫描
introspect the annotations to find out
内省注释以找出
which components you want us to register
您要我们注册哪些组件
but it's also later on all the
但后来也
annotation processes in spring need to
春天的注释过程需要
find out that they have to kick in that
找出他们必须加入
there is some auto wiring to do there is
有一些自动接线要做
some transactional declaration to do we
一些交易声明来做我们
revisited at wholesale there's a totally
批发再造
new implementation for merged annotation
合并注释的新实现
processing with our annotations math
用我们的注释数学处理
annotations that you could override all
您可以覆盖所有注释的注释
of this business a new merged
该业务的新合并
annotations API and plenty of hooks for
注释API和大量的挂钩
optimizing the process I'm going to
优化我要去的过程
elaborate on this in my spring from a
在我的春天，从
partner to talk this afternoon a bit
伙伴今天下午再谈
there is new ground that were covering
有新的领域正在覆盖
in reactive transactions in the
在被动交易中
transaction management space this is a
交易管理空间这是一个
was a bit of the gap in the reactive
在反应性方面有点差距
story before you could do so many things
做很多事情之前的故事
in wet flux in in in other parts of the
在其他部分的湿通量中
framework but what about transactions a
框架，但交易如何
very common question and as of spring
非常普遍的问题，截至春季
filmic five to two the transaction
电影五到二的交易
management processing standard at the
的管理处理标准
natal transaction management at
出生交易管理
imitation is now able to detect the case
模仿现在可以检测到情况
that you are you're trying to decorate a
你正在尝试装饰一个
method that returns a reactive streams
返回反应流的方法
publisher
发布者
we are kicking into a new code path now
我们现在正在进入新的代码路径
if there's a a publisher to decorate
如果有一家出版商来装饰
then we are not doing any threat local
那么我们就不会在本地进行任何威胁
business we are not going into our
我们不从事我们的业务
regular platform transaction manager
常规平台交易经理
mode of operation we go into a distinct
操作模式，我们进入一个独特的
new code path based on a new reactive
基于新反应式的新代码路径
transaction manager spi where we know
我们知道的交易经理SPI
what to do we are applying a
我们正在做什么
transactional operator connected to a
交易运营商连接到
particular backends to your reactive
您的反应式的特定后端
streams publisher and what you get out
流发布者以及您获得的收获
of the call return is actually this
回电的实际上是这个
decorated version of the publisher that
装饰版本的发布者
we prepared for you and there's already
我们为您准备了，已经有
backends in the spring datum or release
后端在春天基准面或释放
train for RT DBC and for MongoDB
培训RT DBC和MongoDB
implementing this reactive transaction
实施此被动交易
management spi this totally new ground
管理SPI这是一个全新的领域
that we are covering in terms of our
就我们而言
socket and this is going to be a topic
套接字，这将是一个主题
later on so I'm not going to tell you
以后我就不告诉你了
much about it this is essentially a new
关于它，这本质上是一个新的
kind of application that you might want
您可能想要的那种应用程序
to build from the spring perspective a
从春天的角度来看
messaging application based on the our
基于我们的消息传递应用程序
socket mechanism this this is an API
套接字机制，这是一个API
that's in development in in
在开发中
collaboration with quite a few companies
与多家公司的合作
out there we are very involved just like
在那里，我们非常参与，就像
the RT DBC effort our socket is the
RT DBC的努力我们的套接字是
other reactive collaborated effort and
其他被动合作
you're going to hear quite a bit about
您将听到很多有关
it later on there's new ground being
后来在新的领域
covered in the Copeland
覆盖在谷轮
landscape we have support for cutting
风景我们有切工支持
coroutines coming and this is going to
协程来了，这将
be featured in just a few in just like
像
half an hour towards the end of this
到此结束半小时
keynote we're going to elaborate on on
主题演讲我们将继续
this part Kotlin is generally a key
这部分Kotlin通常是关键
theme of ours in the spring fabric 5
我们的主题在春季面料5
generation of the project and we are
项目的产生，我们
very eager to pick up the latest and
非常渴望获得最新的
greatest in coupling copying one two
耦合复制一二最大
three core
三芯
means now coming out of experimental
意味着现在脱离实验
into kind of entering its production
进入生产
readiness this there's it's essentially
准备就绪，这基本上是
a mechanism that we are adapting to our
我们正在适应我们的机制
reactive infrastructure underneath the
下方的反应性基础设施
covers so from our perspective it's
涵盖，所以从我们的角度来看，
about usage models it's about
关于它的使用模型
application design questions that can be
可能是应用程序设计问题
addressed nicely by using co-routines in
通过使用协程很好地解决
Kotlin translated to the same underlying
Kotlin翻译成相同的基础
infrastructure so it's a usage it's
基础设施，这是一种用法
another usage model for general
通用的另一种使用模式
infrastructure we hit that we had in
我们所拥有的基础设施
spring from Agra 500 already and last
来自阿格拉500的春天已经过去了
but not least we completed a bit of a
但同样重要的是，我们完成了
closely gap right in in our web
在我们的网络中紧密地差距
architecture in our web framework
Web框架中的架构
offerings there was a functional version
产品有一个功能版本
of Webb flux ever since 5-2 though as a
自5-2以来的Webb流量
five to two days now a functional
现在需要五到两天
version of the servlet based equivalents
基于Servlet的等效版本
dubbed web MVC event here it's
被称为Web MVC事件的是
essentially the same story as functional
本质上与功能相同
wet flux for the traditional web MVC
传统卷筒纸MVC的湿通量
infrastructure based on the survey the
基于调查的基础设施
API so this kind of a annotation based
API，因此基于注释
and the functional variant of both of
以及两者的功能变体
those web stacks now just for a little
这些网页堆栈现在只需要一点
bit of an outlook there's going to be a
一点点的前景将是
spring time at five four three iteration
五四三迭代的春天
this is already very much in the plan
这已经在计划中了
towards the second quarter of next year
即将到明年第二季度
so similar iteration as the e v 1 and v
这样的迭代与ev 1和v
2 iterations there's a few obvious
2次迭代有一些明显的
things we're going to do we're going to
我们要做的事情
support the latest JDK or the latest
支持最新的JDK或最新的
shady case at that point 13 coming up in
当时的阴暗案件13
September then 14 in March and 15 next
9月，然后是3月14日，然后是15日
September so we are going to do
九月，所以我们要做
everything we can to be on the latest
我们可以做到的所有最新信息
shape to be a good citizen on the data
成为数据上的好公民
steady case we have a collaborated F
稳定的情况下，我们有一个合作的F
collaborative effort with the likes of
像
Google and chat brains about code
Google和有关代码的聊天头脑
analysis annotations this is very
分析注释，这是非常
related to what we did in spring for
与我们在春季所做的有关
mock FIFO introducing malleable
模拟FIFO引入可延展性
inaudible model another ability
听不清模型的另一种能力
decorations null safety and the API
装饰无效安全性和API
design on our end these are proper
在我们这端设计这些是正确的
well-defined annotations replacing the
定义明确的注释取代了
chaser 305 arrangement that some tools
追赶者305安排一些工具
use to detect NAT ability declarations
用于检测NAT能力声明
in the API and this is a collaborative
在API中，这是一个协作
project that we're involved in we mean
我们参与的项目意味着
to adopt these new meta annotations if
在以下情况下采用这些新的元注释
we can in the 5.3 time frame there's a a
我们可以在5.3时间范围内
topic that is worth and I just say an
值得的话题，我只是说一个
entire session easily growl VM native
整个会话轻松地咆哮VM本机
images on its substrate vm project the
基板vm上的图像投影
the efforts towards compatibility with
与之兼容的努力
native images ongoing we we are already
本地图像正在进行中，我们已经
have pretty elaborate prototypes we are
我们有非常精致的原型
very involved with the oracle ground vm
非常参与oracle地面vm
team so we're it's a very interesting
团队，所以我们很有趣
also collaboration of sorts towards
也进行各种合作
getting spring ready under certain
在一定条件下准备春天
conditions to build spring applications
建立弹簧应用程序的条件
that can be deployed as native images
可以部署为本地映像
since the native image modeling Ralphie
自从原始图像建模Ralphie
M is still a Developer Preview it's for
M仍是开发人员预览版
early adopters the current ground vm 19
早期采用者目前的虚拟机19
GA does not ship it in production form
GA不会以生产形式发货
this is going to be a topic there's
这将是一个话题
going to be with us towards 5 to 3 next
接下来将要和我们在一起5到3
year we're going to do everything we can
一年，我们将竭尽所能
to allow you to design spring based
让您设计基于弹簧的
applications to be deployed to native
部署到本地的应用程序
images we're going to see where the
图片，我们将要看到
technical challenges remain but with the
技术挑战依然存在，但是
willingness of the ground being timid
胆怯的地面意愿
Oracle to work with us and to address
Oracle与我们合作并解决
kind of the shortcomings of growl in a
那种咆哮的缺点
typical modern enterprise application
典型的现代企业应用
built on spring I'm convinced we're
我相信我们是在春天建造的
going to get somewhere so there's a new
要去某个地方，所以有一个新的
version of having it coming up that we
即将出现的版本
are waiting on that we're going to pick
正在等待我们要选择
up in the 5 to 3 time frame or m6 the
在5至3个时间范围内或m6
first major release in several years
几年来的第一个主要版本
we're always eager to embrace the latest
我们总是渴望拥抱最新
and greatest coming out of the open
和最大的公开
source ecosystem out there
源生态系统
this is having a door em we all
我们所有人都有一扇门
waiting on a new Jackson release for
等待新的Jackson发行
what it's worth and and several others
它的价值，还有其他几个
there's code lien 1.4 we in close
有代码留置权1.4，我们接近
interaction with the coupling team we
与联队的互动
always wants to be kind of ahead of the
总是想领先于
curve in knowing what's coming in Kotlin
了解Kotlin即将发生的变化
so the five four three timeframe should
所以五四三的时间框架应该
work fine for this and that's another
为此工作很好，那是另一个
piece that we are eagerly waiting on
我们急切等待的一块
that JD ten served it for best version
JD十最佳版本
of chedi still no doubt but in the five
的契迪无疑仍然是，但在五个
the three time frame we're going to pick
我们要选择的三个时间范围
it up pretty pretty quickly there's a
很快就出现了
few things we are not going to tackle
我们不会处理的几件事
and that's what i'm going to leave you
那就是我要离开你的
with here strategic topics that are not
这里的战略主题不是
likely to make it in five x but they are
可能达到五倍，但它们是
in the back of our minds so don't expect
在我们的心中，所以不要指望
to spring from a five something release
从五个东西释放
bringing those onto your table but rest
把那些带到你的桌子上，但休息
assured today they are on our roadmap
今天放心，他们在我们的路线图上
they are in the back of our minds we are
他们在我们的脑海中
trying to anticipate what kind of impact
试图预测什么样的影响
they would have on to our roadmap acidic
他们将不得不坚持我们的路线图
eleven baseline not coming all that
十一基线不是全部
quickly spring from mcfife is going to
迅速从mcfife反弹
remain based on JDK 8 can be used in JDK
仍基于JDK 8可以在JDK中使用
eleven and newer but it's not going to
11和更新，但不会
require 3d key eleven this is only going
需要3d键十一这只会
to come in a subsequent release a spring
即将发布的春天
filmic six of sorts we are we don't have
我们没有的六种电影
immediate intentions to bring anything
立即带任何东西的意图
new on to the table for the module
模块表上的新内容
system that Java nine brought into the
Java 9引入的系统
world spring as it is can be used in
可以使用世界弹簧
custom architectures using the module
使用模块的定制架构
system already but there's no no out of
系统已经存在，但没有没有可能
the box stories of ours that are coming
我们即将来的盒子故事
in 5x according to the current plan this
按照目前的计划5倍
is going to be revisited at a later
稍后将重新讨论
point and another topic that is with us
要点和我们在一起的另一个话题
for a few years already
已经有几年了
Jakarta EE the transfer of the former
雅加达EE前者的转让
Java EE specifications to the Eclipse
Eclipse的Java EE规范
Foundation and any new revisions of the
基金会及其任何新修订
API is possibly in a new name space in a
API可能在新名称空间中
new Jakarta namespace instead of G of X
新的Jakarta命名空间，而不是X的G
this is very much a topic that we're
这是我们非常关注的话题
following but
跟随但
no change of the arrangement is expected
预计不会改变安排
for springtime ik 5x we're going to
对于春季ik 5x，我们将
remain Java X space based on the Java EE
保留基于Java EE的Java X空间
8 level of the API so that for the OJ pa
API的8级，以便用于OJ pa
to the two bean validation to the DOE so
到DOE验证两个bean
no change in the story for 5x but
5倍的故事没有变化，但
something's going to come at some point
某些时候会发生什么
when there's new infrastructure to be
当有新的基础设施时
picked up coming out of the Eclipse
从日食中捡起
Foundation or coming coming out coming
地基或现身现身
with those Jakarta EE api's as the
以那些Jakarta EE api作为
primary interaction model and last but
主要互动模型和最后但
not least there's project loom fighters
至少有项目织机战士
a research project in the JDK absolutely
绝对是JDK中的一个研究项目
this might be a game-changer in many
这可能是许多游戏规则的改变者
ways in terms of the architectures that
就架构而言
we can build and the efficiency of those
我们可以建立和那些人的效率
architectures if you're using an
架构（如果您使用的是
imperative programming style very well
命令式编程风格很好
very much following what's happening
非常关注正在发生的事情
there but it's not going to come to the
在那里，但它不会来到
JDK so that we could consume it anytime
JDK，以便我们可以随时使用它
soon we're going where we're waiting on
很快我们要去等待的地方
something to materialize there we're
在这里实现的东西
going to pick it up in a later spring
以后的春天去捡
time of generation for sure all right
肯定的世代时间
but first things first we're going to
但是首先我们要去
deliver a spring format 5 - 2 GA to you
为您提供5-2 GA的春季规格
in July this year so I hope there's
今年七月，所以我希望
plenty of goodness for you to pick up in
有很多好处可以让你
that generation of the framework and the
那一代的框架和
corresponding spring boot to the to
相应的弹簧靴到
release so I hope you're in hope you're
释放，所以我希望你在希望你在
agree with the focus that we chose to
同意我们选择的重点
set for this particular generation and
为这一代人而设
we're going to go into more depth now in
我们现在将更深入
terms of the reactive story and the
反应性故事和
quarantine story in the next two
下两个隔离的故事
sections of the keynote so let me
主题演讲的各个部分，让我
welcome we letter and Bend on to the
欢迎我们来信并弯曲到
stage please
请登台
right the stage is yours thank you yes
正确的舞台是你的，谢谢
we do
我们的确是
quick laptop slip here or switch here so
快速笔记本电脑滑到这里或切换到这里，所以
that we can do some demos for you all
我们可以为大家做一些演示
while we're taking care of that this is
而我们正在照顾这是
actually my first time to Barcelona and
实际上我第一次去巴塞罗那
I have always known that it's an amazing
我一直都知道这很棒
city to visit for tourism and things
观光旅游的城市
like that but I'm a huge cyclist and I
那样，但是我是一个伟大的自行车手，我
was absolutely amazed I flew my bike all
我真的很惊讶
the way over here from San Francisco in
从旧金山到这里的路
the last three days I've been out
最近三天我出去了
cycling you're constantly in the
骑自行车，你一直在
mountains around here and it is
这里周围的山脉是
absolutely amazing all the little towns
绝对让所有小城镇惊艳
all the great mountains so if you are
所有的大山，如果你是
also a cyclist I highly recommend
也是我强烈推荐的自行车手
Barcelona as a destination to to go some
巴塞罗那是去的目的地
slides there we go great so thank you
幻灯片在那里，我们走的很好，谢谢
everyone
大家
as Juergen introduced us my name is Ben
正如Juergen向我们介绍的那样，我叫Ben
Hale I'm the lead of the Cloud Foundry
Hale我是Cloud Foundry的负责人
Java experience so I run all of Java on
Java经验，所以我在Java上运行所有Java
the pivotal cloud platform and with me I
关键的云平台，和我一起
have Violetta and Violetta is the
有Violetta和Violetta是
reactor core team member and the lead of
反应堆核心小组成员和负责人
reactor nettie and that's going to come
反应堆网络连接，这将要发生
up importantly in a couple seconds here
在几秒钟内重要地上升
so if we take a look back over the last
因此，如果我们回顾一下过去
three years or so the spring team has
三年左右的春季队有
been coming to you and saying reactive
来找你说反应
reactive reactive right like three years
反应性权利，像三年
ago we said there's this thing called
之前我们说有一个东西叫做
project reactor that we sort of rebooted
我们有点重启的项目反应堆
from another project and we said this is
来自另一个项目，我们说这是
a real thing that we're gonna put a team
我们要组成一个团队的真实事物
on we're gonna exert a lot of energy
在我们身上会消耗很多精力
into this then two years ago or maybe
大概两年前
one year ago let's say it that way the
一年前让我们这样说
spring team came with spring Webb flux
春季团队带来了春季韦伯助焊剂
which is you know sort of a reactive way
你知道这是一种反应方式
to write web applications all right this
编写Web应用程序就可以了
year I'm gonna be on stage talking to
我要在舞台上与之交谈
you about reactive a little bit more but
您的反应性要高一些，但是
the question is why right all of us have
问题是为什么我们所有人都有
been Java developers some for a couple
曾经是Java开发人员
of years me I've been one for 15 16
我几年来一直15 16
years now why all of a sudden is there
多年以来为什么突然出现
this focus on on reactive
专注于反应性
and the answer is that the spring team
答案是春季队
generally and really the broader Java
一般而言，实际上是更广泛的Java
ecosystem at this point has identified
此时的生态系统已经确定
reactive programming as the next
下一个反应式编程
frontier for high efficiency
高效率的前沿
applications and this is something that
应用程序，这是
for many many years we didn't really
许多年来我们并没有真正
care all that much about efficiency was
非常关心效率是
well I had a data center I threw a war
好吧，我有一个数据中心，我打了一场战争
over the wall to somebody running a
在墙上跑来跑去的人
tomcat and that person needed to scale
tomcat，那个人需要扩展
Tomcat I didn't have a whole lot of
Tomcat我没有很多
visibility into it but a lot of the new
可见性，但很多新
sort of cloud architectures are running
某种云架构正在运行
a lot more applications where
还有更多的应用
horizontally scaling those applications
水平扩展这些应用程序
and more importantly we're probably
更重要的是，我们可能
paying a very large bill for this kind
为此付出了非常大的账单
of stuff now all of a sudden efficiency
现在突然有了效率
starts coming back to us
开始回到我们身边
so the fundamental non-blocking nature
所以基本的非阻塞性
and optionally it's asynchronous
并且可以选择异步
behavior make better uses of the
行为可以更好地利用
resources that we are given or that we
我们获得的资源或我们
are out there paying for so instead of
在那里付款，而不是
having an application where you might be
在您可能拥有的应用程序中
running Tomcat with its 200 threads
使用200个线程运行Tomcat
which means you can only get 200
这意味着你只能得到200
connections and so you're forced to sort
连接，所以您不得不进行排序
of horizontally scale your application
水平扩展您的应用程序
so you've got 10 instances or 15
所以你有10个实例或15个实例
instances or 20 instances but all of
个实例或20个实例，但全部
those instances are like 10 or 15% CPU
这些实例就像10％或15％的CPU
because you're really connection bound
因为你真的是连接受限
this idea of reactive programming
反应式编程的想法
something like web flux is that now of a
像网络流量这样的东西现在
sudden we can support tens of thousands
突然我们可以支持成千上万
of connections but we're only going to
连接，但我们只会
do it for the number of physical threads
根据物理线程数执行此操作
available to us now all of a sudden it's
现在突然可供我们使用
a totally reasonable thing to start
完全合理的开始
running our instances near 100% CPU
在100％CPU上运行我们的实例
because when we're waiting for things
因为当我们等待的时候
were not blocking but the other really
没有阻止，但另一个真的
key thing that reactive brings to us
反应性带给我们的关键
beyond just sort of this non-blocking
不仅仅是这种非阻塞
asynchronous behavior is the fact that
异步行为是事实
we can now tame tail latency by tail
我们现在可以逐尾驯服尾巴延迟
latency what I mean is a lot of us when
延迟我的意思是我们很多时候
we take a look at our metrics what we
我们来看一下我们的指标
see is what's my 75th percentile what's
看到我的百分之七十五是什么
my 90th percentile what's my 99th
我的百分之九十是我的百分之九十九
percentile how quickly are we responding
百分位数，我们响应速度有多快
to our in the fastest instance to our
在最快的情况下
customers but really what you would many
客户，但实际上您会
of sort of the that large scale cloud
那种大规模的云
companies have twigged on is it you want
公司已经在想你想要的
to sort of look at it in the other
在另一个方面看一下
direction as well what's the worst
方向也最糟
possible case that people are seeing
人们可能看到的情况
maybe I can service most of my customers
也许我可以为大多数客户提供服务
and a hundred milliseconds or two
一两百毫秒
milliseconds but if my worst-case
毫秒，但如果我的情况最糟
scenario for a customer is that it's
客户的情况是
actually gonna take me you know an
其实要带我你知道
entire second to respond that's just as
整整一秒钟做出回应，就像
bad and the thing that we want to to be
坏事和我们想要成为的事情
able to get a hold of so all of these
能够掌握所有这些
things right like all of the benefits we
像我们所有的好处一样正确的事情
see about reactive have led us to seeing
看到关于反应的引导我们
code like this now right this is whether
这样的代码现在是
sorry web flux method that knows how to
抱歉，网络通量方法知道如何
go off using springs web client and
使用Springs Web Client退出并
asynchronously and non-blocking make a
异步和非阻塞使
call to two other web services wait for
调用另外两个Web服务等待
them to come back coordinate the return
他们回来协调回报
value transform it into whatever this
价值将其转化为
composite thing is this is now a viable
复合的东西是现在这是可行的
thing that we see lots and lots of
我们看到很多很多的东西
developers doing already today right if
开发人员今天已经在做，如果
you would stood up here three years ago
你三年前会在这里站起来
and I showed this code to somebody
然后我向别人展示了这段代码
they'd have no idea what they were doing
他们不知道自己在做什么
or why it's important but now we see
或为什么它很重要，但现在我们看到了
that it is so what is still needed then
就是这样，那么仍然需要什么
right like we've given you web flux
就像我们给您的网络流量一样
we've done project reactor we've really
我们已经完成了项目反应堆
knocked down a lot of the low-hanging
击倒了很多低迷的人
fruit here but we said you know we took
水果在这里，但我们说你知道我们吃了
a step back last year and said okay if
去年退后一步说，如果
we've done this what else can we do to
我们已经做到了，我们还能做什么
help you start on this reactive journey
帮助您开始这一被动的旅程
we identified three big things we're
我们确定了三大问题
going to talk about improvement to
要谈论改善
Raptor core features we're going to talk
我们要谈论的Raptor核心功能
about networking cross process back
关于网络跨进程回
pressure and we're going to talk about
压力，我们将谈论
data access and with that I'm going to
数据访问以及与此相关的
hand it over to Violetta here to talk
交给维奥莱塔在这里谈
about those reactor core features okay
关于那些反应堆的核心特征好吗
it's been already set reactive
它已经被设置为反应性
programming case many benefits and
编程案例有很多好处，
applications are more scalable they use
应用程序使用时更具可扩展性
less resources they are resilient but
弹性较小的资源，但
what happens if we have an issue in our
如果我们遇到问题怎么办
application sometimes it might be very
应用程序有时可能会非常
challenging to find the root cause of
寻找根本原因的挑战
the issue for example with the
这个问题，例如
well-known exceptions in the imperative
当务之急是众所周知的例外
programming where you have the path to
进行编程的地方
the error you can very easily find the
您可以很容易找到该错误
root cause but that's not the case with
根本原因，但事实并非如此
the reactive programming we do not have
我们没有的反应式编程
these exceptions anymore
这些例外了
fortunately with the latest improve
幸运的是有了最新的改进
in the reactor project and Spring
在反应堆项目和春季
Framework we can offer you the bugging
我们可以为您提供漏洞检测的框架
experience similar to what you have in
体验与您所拥有的相似
imperative programming and I will start
命令式编程，我将开始
with reactor the back agent reactor the
带有反应堆的背试剂反应堆
back agent is actually able to provide
后台代理实际上能够提供
you the trace to the arrow this is a
您对箭头的跟踪这是一个
Java agent that makes a bytecode
生成字节码的Java代理
transformation so that you can easily
转换，以便您可以轻松
integrate it in your application and
将其集成到您的应用程序中
also it does not put over additional
也不会把额外的
overhead on your application
应用程序的开销
so using this reactor the back agent you
所以用这个反应堆的后卫你
can even be able to put it in your
甚至可以将其放入您的
production environment and have the
生产环境并具备
missing doubling information even in
即使在
your production applications for today's
您今天的生产应用
keynote I prepared one simple
主题演讲我准备了一个简单的
application and now I will switch to my
应用程序，现在我将切换到我的
ID with this application I will show you
此应用程序的ID，我将向您显示
how you can easily use react to the book
如何轻松使用对书的反应
agent
代理人
but first then do you know that we have
但是首先你知道我们有
so many interesting sessions these two
这两个有趣的环节
days I saw the number that was up there
几天我看到那里的电话号码
and like I want to go to all of these
就像我想去所有这些
sessions yeah this right which to attend
会议是这个参加的权利
because of that I created one very
因此，我创造了一个
simple application which will propose
建议的简单应用
the conference sessions based on
会议会议基于
attending name so let me see what the
参加的名字，所以让我看看
session I should attend let me start the
我应该参加的会议让我开始
application
应用
and now let's four wait for a bit okay
现在让我们四个等一下
the application is actually pretty
该应用程序实际上很漂亮
clever because it proposes to attend my
聪明，因为它建议参加我的
own session it's gonna be a good session
自己的会议，这将是一个很好的会议
but let's see now what the application
现在让我们看看应用程序是什么
will propose for Ben and then you have
向本求婚，然后你有
no pent internal server error sorry
没有pent内部服务器错误对不起
I'm sure I'm doing two sessions right
我确定我要进行两次会议
let me check what's going on here with
让我检查一下这是怎么回事
this application what I can see is
我看到的这个应用程序是
nullpointerexception but that's all I do
nullpointerexception，但这就是我要做的
not know where this exception happens
不知道该异常发生在哪里
how to for example the book this kind of
例如如何将这种书
situations what I see in the stack trace
我在堆栈跟踪中看到的情况
is reactor core called then reactor
被称为反应堆的反应堆堆芯
Nettie and Nettie there is no anything
Nettie和Nettie没有任何东西
for my application code fortunately by
对于我的应用程序代码，幸运的是
default with the latest Spring Framework
默认使用最新的Spring Framework
you will be able to see some checkpoints
您将能够看到一些检查点
at the end and for example here I can
最后，例如在这里我可以
see that most probably this back end
看到最有可能是这个后端
service has some problems but I still
服务有一些问题，但我仍然
cannot say where the null pointer is so
无法说空指针在哪里
let me introduce to my application
让我介绍一下我的申请
reactor the back agent
反应堆背剂
so what we need to do we need only two
所以我们要做的只是两个
changes to the application the first one
更改应用程序的第一个
is obviously to provide dependency to
显然是提供对
the two and the second one is to
第二个和第二个是
initialize the reactor the back agent
初始化反应器的后台代理
because the doctor the back agent will
因为医生后勤人员会
instrument in the classes rewarding it
在课堂上奖励它
is better to put it in my main metal so
最好放在我的主要金属上
it is here and let me start now the
它在这里，让我现在开始
applications with this agent
该代理程序的应用
if I request it again I should be able
如果我再次请求，我应该能够
to see more information for the problem
查看有关该问题的更多信息
so again I can find my handler here in
所以我可以再次在这里找到我的处理程序
the check points but as you can see I
检查点，但正如你所见
have a lot more information and now I
有很多信息，现在我
even can see that this handler tries to
甚至可以看到此处理程序试图
write the response and at some point of
写下回应，并在
time this session repository may be
此会话存储库的时间
returns this no pointer exception with
返回此无指针异常
this tech trace we can even navigate to
我们甚至可以导航到此技术跟踪
the source code and actually I can see
源代码，实际上我可以看到
that this publisher here has a problem
这个发布者有问题
let me see what is the what we have in
让我看看我们拥有什么
the initialization phase and yeah I did
初始化阶段，是的，我做了
very stupid mistake here let me fix it
非常愚蠢的错误在这里让我解决
very quickly
很快
and now the session for Ben should be
现在Ben的会议应该是
practice ratio relational database
练习比率关系数据库
connectivity right okay the next two
连接正确，接下来的两个
that I would like to introduce you is
我想介绍给你的是
block count as I already said with
正如我已经说过的
reactive programming we use less threats
响应式编程，我们使用更少的威胁
and it's really really important to not
真的很重要
block them however it is not only the
阻止他们，但不仅
code that you as developers write but it
您作为开发人员编写的代码，但是
is also the third party libraries that
也是第三方图书馆
you may use so you cannot guarantee that
您可以使用，所以您不能保证
the whole code will not use blocking
整个代码不会使用阻塞
calls and it is important to have some
电话，重要的是要有一些
automatic tools that can detect whether
可以检测是否有自动工具
it is in your application or in your
它在您的应用程序或您的
third-party library whether you have a
第三方图书馆是否有
blocking call block count is such - it
阻止呼叫阻止计数是这样的-它
is a Java agent which instruments the
是Java代理，用于
JVM classes and intercepts the blocking
JVM类并拦截阻塞
calls when they are interests with non
当他们对非
blocking operations only and what we
仅阻止运营以及我们
recommend you is to use these two while
建议您使用这两个时间
we were testing for validating your
我们正在测试以验证您的
application so that you will be sure
应用程序，以便您可以确定
that there is no working code in the
没有工作代码
whole chain now I will try to use block
现在整个链我将尝试使用块
count with my application
算上我的申请
it is again very easy to use it what we
再次使用它非常容易
need is a dependency to block count and
需要依赖于阻止计数，并且
then we need also to initialize it in
然后我们还需要初始化它
our main method now let's start the
现在我们主要的方法开始
application with block count
带块数的应用
and requested oops the real them the
并要求哎呀，真正的他们
live demo okay let me try again to stop
现场演示好吧，让我再试一次
this one and this one and start it again
这个和这个，然后重新开始
okay this time we can see that actually
好的，这次我们可以看到
we have some blocking coal in our
我们有一些煤块
application and it does some socket
应用程序，它做了一些套接字
connect let's check what which component
连接，让我们检查一下哪个组件
does it if I go again to the logs I will
如果我再次转到日志，我会这样做
see here that actually it is the rest
看到这里实际上是其余的
template that does this block in coal
在煤中执行此操作的模板
because rest template as you know is a
因为您知道的其余模板是一个
blocking HTTP coil and we use the rest
阻止HTTP线圈，其余的我们使用
template for our remote calls so in
我们的远程呼叫模板
order to fix that I can easily switch
为了解决我可以轻松切换的问题
from rest template to web client which
从其余模板到Web客户端
is a non-blocking interactive fetched
是非阻塞的交互式抓取
required so let me do this and see what
需要，所以让我这样做，看看
will be the result
将是结果
so we to a point my application is
所以我们要说的是
working again let me switch again to the
再次工作，让我再次切换到
presentation a summary you can see that
演示摘要，您可以看到
using reactor the BOK agent and block
使用反应堆中的BOK代理并阻止
count I was able to identify and fix to
我能够确定并解决的问题
severe problems in my application for
我申请的严重问题
five minutes but this is not this tool
五分钟，但这不是这个工具
libraries are not the only one that we
图书馆不是我们唯一的图书馆
can provide you we have new operators
可以为您提供新的运营商
new hooks in the reactor core with
反应堆堆芯中的新钩子
tractor nettie we have performance
拖拉机网我们有表现
improvements and this is not it's not
改进，这不是，不是
only this but we plan more enhancements
仅此，但我们计划进行更多增强
in the future in order to be able to
为了将来能够
make the development experience better
改善开发经验
so with depth then I will hand over to
所以我会深入
you to continue with the reactive story
您继续讲故事
and the improvements that we have there
以及我们在那里所做的改进
great thank you very much
非常感谢你
so reactor core improvements well that's
所以反应堆堆芯的改进很好
not good
不好
well reactor core improvements are
改进反应堆堆芯
obviously very very important but there
显然非常重要，但是
are other things that you want to do
您还想做其他事情
right the first one being this idea of
对，第一个是这个想法
cross process back pressure reactive
跨过程反压反应
streams is a great API and a great
streams是一个很棒的API，也是一个很棒的
specification for discussing how
讨论如何规范
publishers and subscribers are allowed
允许发布者和订阅者
to send and consume data between one
在一个之间发送和使用数据
another but at the end of the jvm you
另一个，但是在jvm的结尾
sort of lose that there's no way to
有点失去，没有办法
communicate and a micro service
沟通和微服务
architecture that same demand beyond
相同需求之外的架构
that point so over the years obviously
这一点多年来很明显
the entire industry has standardized on
整个行业已经标准化
HTTP as the protocol for network
HTTP作为网络协议
interaction and for a great many things
互动以及很多事情
this is good enough but when you start
这足够好，但是当您开始时
taking a look at these projects these
看看这些项目这些
really high efficiency really high
效率很高效率很高
throughput kinds of projects and micro
吞吐量项目和微型项目
service networks we find that there are
服务网络，我们发现
really big problems with HTTP stemming
HTTP阻止的真正大问题
mostly from its you know sort of its
大部分是从它你知道它的
roots as I want to go get a page of text
我想去的根得到一页文字
and that's it because we don't really
就是这样，因为我们不是真的
send a lot of pages of text anymore so
发送大量的文本了，所以
if you take a look maybe an HTTP 1.0 we
如果您看一下HTTP 1.0，
have single request connections are
具有单个请求连接
horribly efficient and we introduce HTTP
非常高效，我们引入了HTTP
1.1 but even that has issues because
1.1，但即使那样也有问题，因为
pipelining right the way you're supposed
按照您应该的方式进行流水线操作
to use connections with multiple
使用多个连接
requests on them has head-of-line
对他们的要求有负责人
blocking problems and it's really really
阻止问题，这是真的
too difficult generally we also see that
太难了，我们也看到了
to make HTTP reliable you end up using
使HTTP可靠，您最终使用
patterns like a circuit breaker pattern
像断路器模式一样的模式
and you end up using external systems
最终导致您使用外部系统
like histor extend and turbine and
像历史记录程序扩展和涡轮
things like that just to keep your
这样的事情只是为了保持你的
system reliable and it's almost
系统可靠，几乎
certainly not a good strategy to make
当然不是一个好的策略
one service reliable by starting two or
通过启动两项或一项可靠的服务
three other services because you have to
其他三项服务，因为您必须
keep them reliable as well and it's just
保持它们的可靠性，这仅仅是
Turtles the whole way down and then
整个乌龟，然后
probably in today's day and age for so
大概在今天的时代
many of the applications that exists in
存在于其中的许多应用程序
the world it's limited to this
世界仅限于此
request/response kind of model HTTP 2
请求/响应类型HTTP 2
loosens this up a bit but not really
放松一点但不是真的
significantly and so the spring team
如此显着，春季队
engaged a little more than a year ago on
订婚一年多一点
a project called our socket or
一个称为我们的套接字或
socket was originally a protocol so it's
套接字最初是一个协议，所以它是
a network protocol much like HTTP and it
一个非常像HTTP的网络协议
was originally developed inside of
最初是在
Netflix and as the the Netflix team sort
Netflix和Netflix团队的排序
of broke up a bit they moved out and
分手了一点，他们搬了出去，
they started taking it other places so
他们开始把它带到其他地方，所以
it's really heavily used in places like
它确实在诸如
startup we work with net if I it's used
初创公司，如果我使用过，我们将与net合作
very heavily at Facebook as well and so
在Facebook上也很忙
our socket is in a very long sentence a
我们的插座用很长的句子
bi-directional multiplexed message based
基于双向复用消息
binary protocol based on reactive
基于反应式的二进制协议
streams back pressure and that's a lot
流回压力，这很多
of stuff there's gonna be a session on
将会有一个会议
this if it's something that might
如果这可能
interest you but the key takeaways from
使您感兴趣，但关键要点
thinking about our socket is that it
考虑我们的插座是
actually encapsulates more than one
实际上封装了多个
interaction model it's already
交互模型已经
encapsulates the idea of request
封装了请求的思想
response which we already know but
我们已经知道的回应，但是
fire-and-forget maybe you need to send a
一劳永逸也许您需要发送
bunch of logs from a client device back
一堆来自客户端设备的日志
and they don't care if it gets delivered
他们不在乎它是否交付
request stream which is I think what
请求流，我认为是什么
most of us do these days I'm gonna send
这些天我们大多数人都会发送
you a request and I want you to stream
给您一个请求，我希望您流式传输
me a bunch of data and then finally
给我一堆数据，然后终于
channel which is anything goes there's a
通道什么都有，有一个
big old pipe and you can just send data
大旧管道，您可以发送数据
as you wish between two parties from
如您所愿，两方之间
that point the language itself sorry not
那一点语言本身对不起
the language the protocol itself is also
协议本身的语言也是
really flexible its language agnostic
真正灵活的语言不可知论
there are many many bindings for it its
它有很多绑定
payload agnostic right so it's not just
有效负载不可知的权利，而不仅仅是
HTTP it's not Jason it's not in this
HTTP，不是Jason，不是
case of something like G RPC just
像G RPC这样的情况
protobufs you can send all of these
protobufs您可以发送所有这些
things across the the protocol it's also
整个协议中的事情
transport agnostic so if you're lucky
与运输无关，所以如果你幸运的话
enough to have an internal network in
足以拥有一个内部网络
your data center where you can safely
您可以安全使用的数据中心
send TCP data you can do that but you're
发送TCP数据，你可以做到，但你是
not limited to it you can stream it out
不限于此，您可以将其流式传输
to the open world over WebSockets or
通过WebSockets进入开放世界或
HTTP - you can use air on if you need
HTTP-如果需要，可以使用air
the unbelievable fastest possible thing
令人难以置信的最快的事情
you can get over UDP as well and we also
您也可以通过UDP，我们也
have done a lot of work on the spring
在春季做了很多工作
side to make sure that our socket is
一边确保我们的插座是
programming model agnostic you can use
可以使用不可知的编程模型
the direct our socket API you can use
您可以直接使用我们的套接字API
RPC and a protobuf style very similar to
RPC和protobuf样式非常相似
G RPC if that's what you want to do but
G RPC如果您要这样做，但是
you can also use a messaging style which
您还可以使用一种消息传递样式
is something that spring really endorses
是春天真正认可的东西
obviously from you know our history with
显然，从您那里了解我们的历史
message handlers and and controllers so
消息处理程序和控制器
we've got a network protocol that can
我们有一个网络协议可以
help you along this reactive journey oh
帮助您进行这一被动的旅程哦
sorry
抱歉
they're a bunch of other protocol
他们是一堆其他协议
they're a bunch of other features as
他们还有很多其他功能
well resume ability probably being the
良好的恢复能力可能是
biggest one Facebook has use this to
Facebook最大的一家公司已经使用它来
great effects for example so that when a
效果很好，例如
network connection drops momentarily
网络连接暂时断开
when it comes back on rather than having
当它回来而不是
to try and resync state from where it
尝试从那里重新同步状态
was exactly instead it'll now say hey
恰恰相反，它现在会说嘿
I've been gone for the last hundred
我已经走了最后一百
milliseconds to tell me what happened
毫秒告诉我发生了什么
since last time I saw you so we have a
自从上次见到你以来，我们有一个
network protocol that can help you along
可以帮助您的网络协议
the reactive journey but then the very
反应性的旅程，但随后
last thing that we're going to talk
我们要谈的最后一件事
about here today is something very very
今天在这里非常非常
near and dear to my heart when we talk
当我们交谈时，我的心就亲近了
to customers a lot about reactive
给客户很多关于反应式的
programming especially the customers
编程尤其是客户
that haven't actually gone to production
尚未真正投产的
with it
用它
we always hear this idea that reactive
我们总是听到这种反应
data access is problematic for them so
数据访问对他们来说是有问题的，所以
today most of our customers who are on
今天我们大多数的客户
reactive stacks and doing reactive
反应堆和反应堆
applications in production use no sequel
生产中的应用没有续集
data stores right these are sort of new
数据存储对，这些都是新的
very sort of forward thinking kinds of
非常有远见的
services and they really embrace these
服务，他们真的拥抱这些
new sort of forward-thinking
新型的前瞻性思维
non-blocking
非阻塞
asynchronous kind of programming model
异步编程模型
so MongoDB Apache Cassandra Couchbase
所以MongoDB Apache Cassandra Couchbase
Redis all of these things are services
Redis所有这些都是服务
where there are Java client drivers that
有Java客户端驱动程序的地方
can work in a reactive world but the
可以在反应性世界中工作，但是
most common data store is missing most
最常见的数据存储丢失最多
common data store by fine by far it's
到目前为止，通用数据存储是
just those top ones you may think
你可能会想到的那些顶级
they're very sexy and everything but
他们非常性感，除了
they're just a really small fraction of
他们只是一小部分
all of the data currently stored or
当前存储的所有数据或
currently processed in our industry most
目前在我们行业中加工最多
common data store obviously relational
通用数据存储显然是相关的
databases it's where all the data has
数据库是所有数据所在的地方
been sent for the last 30 years and it's
被发送了最近30年，
exactly where all that data is still
确切地说所有数据仍然在哪里
currently sitting and all of you have
目前坐着，你们所有人都有
applications that need to interact with
需要与之交互的应用程序
them so we started a project called r2
他们，所以我们启动了一个名为r2的项目
DBC our two DBC is reactive relational
DBC我们两个DBC是反应性的关系
database connectivity quite a handful
数据库连接很少
just remember the Droid logo r2 DBC is
只要记住Droid徽标r2 DBC是
at its very base an API designed from
从根本上说，
the ground up for reactive programming
反应式编程的基础
because simply wrapping
因为只是包装
isn't sufficient right JDBC is a
是不够的，JDBC是一个
blocking API it's an imperative API even
阻止API甚至是命令式API
putting it into thread pool has problems
将其放入线程池有问题
with either pool exhaustion or resource
池耗尽或资源不足
exhaustion that will lead to those
用尽会导致那些
scenarios where you end up blocking
您最终阻止的情况
inside of a thread pool so we can't do
在线程池中，所以我们不能做
that we need to start from scratch and
我们需要从头开始，
it's got some really strong design
它有一些非常坚固的设计
principles that go along with it
随之而来的原则
first and foremost utilize reactive
首先是利用反应
streams and sorry reactive streams types
流和对不起的反应流类型
and patterns we want this to be native
和模式，我们希望这是本地的
to the reactive world straight off the
直接进入反应世界
bat we want it to be completely blocking
蝙蝠，我们希望它被完全阻挡
sorry non blocking all the way to the
很抱歉，一路无路
database and we go even further than
数据库，我们走得更远
that some wire protocols some of the
一些有线协议的一些
protocols that database clients connect
数据库客户端连接的协议
to databases with have the ability to do
有能力去做的数据库
sort of reactive style back pressure I'm
我有点反应风格的背压
most familiar with Postgres it's the one
最了解Postgres的那个
that I've implemented and for example
我已经实现的，例如
you can simply say send me the next 10
您可以简单地说下10个寄给我
items and send me the next hundred and
物品，然后再寄给我
twenty-eight items and the database
二十八项和数据库
doesn't even materialize that out of the
甚至没有实现
disk until you've asked for the next
磁盘，直到您要求下一个
number of items and that way you have a
项目数量，这样您就可以
nice controlled way to get data into a
一种很好的受控方式将数据导入
client we also want to shrink these
客户我们也想缩小这些
drivers to the smallest possible they
将驱动程序最小化
can be even if that affects sort of
即使那会影响某种
human usability we want to have a very
人类的可用性，我们希望拥有一个非常
small surface area so database vendors
表面积小，因此数据库供应商
have the easiest possible thing to
有最容易的事情
implement and then we want to enable we
实施，然后我们要启用我们
want to make sure that the API that
要确保该API
we've designed here also enables
我们在这里设计的还可以
multiple humane api's right we expect
我们期望多种人性化的api的权利
our two DB C is for database vendors and
我们的两个DB C是针对数据库供应商的，
we want other clients to be created on
我们希望在其他客户上创建
top of it I don't know if you're the
最重要的是，我不知道你是否是
kind of person who likes mybatis where
那种喜欢mybatis的人
you write a lot of sequel statements or
你写了很多续集声明，或者
you a JPA kind of person where you deal
您是您交易的JPA类人
with objects or you a JD bi person where
与对象或您是JD bi人，
you like a really fluent API instead I
您喜欢一个真正流利的API，而我
want all of these things to be possible
希望所有这些事情成为可能
on top of a single driver API so today
在单个驱动程序API之上，所以今天
our 2d VC has a bunch of driver
我们的2D VC有很多驱动程序
implementations we have h2 Microsoft
我们拥有H2 Microsoft的实现
sequel Postgres my sequel has come out
续集Postgres我的续集问世了
of the community so we're really really
社区，所以我们真的是
happy about that one huge numbers of
为那一大批人感到高兴
type conversions sort of on the
类型转换
equivalence of the the JDBC drivers of
JDBC驱动程序的等效性
those things blob and CLOB support save
blob和CLOB支持保存的那些东西
points and making use of that new
点和利用新
transaction functionality that Jurgen
Jurgen的交易功能
described in the Spring Framework
在Spring框架中描述
we have reactive transactions as well we
我们也有被动交易
also took a look to the or sorry we also
还看了一下，还是对不起我们
talked to the broader Java community
与更广泛的Java社区进行了交谈
things like APM vendors and things like
像APM供应商之类的东西
that and said if you could change things
并说如果你可以改变的话
about JDBC if you had a chance to start
有关JDBC的信息，如果您有机会开始
again what would you like to see and one
再次，你想看到什么，一个
of their key principles was they really
他们的主要原则是
really wanted to see first-class
真的很想看一流
observability they wanted to know that
可观察性他们想知道
they could inspect all the things that
他们可以检查所有的东西
their customers expected right in a very
他们的客户非常期待
easy way apparently today for APM
今天显然是APM的简便方法
vendors to to observe JDBC is just a
供应商观察到的JDBC只是一个
giant problem for them we wanted to make
我们想为他们解决的巨大问题
sure that we had really first-class
确保我们真的是一流的
connection pooling it turns out
连接池事实证明
connection pooling and a non-blocking
连接池和非阻塞
environment is really really difficult
环境真的很困难
and the reactor team has been absolutely
反应堆团队已经绝对
amazing creating a new project called
创建一个名为
reactor fuel that we're able to utilize
我们能够利用的反应堆燃料
and get really high efficiency pooling
并获得真正高效的汇总
and we also already have some client
而且我们已经有一些客户
implementation spring data was the very
实施春季数据非常
first person basically to jump on top of
第一人称基本上跳到
this API and so if you're familiar with
该API，因此，如果您熟悉
Spring data's repository style of data
Spring Data的数据存储库样式
access that's already available to you
您已经可以使用的访问权限
but we see in the broader community
但我们在更广泛的社区中看到
again beyond that juke JDI mybatis are
再说那个JKE JDI mybatis
already all taking a look at the r2 DBC
已经都在看r2 DBC
api and in fact I just came from DevOps
api，实际上我只是来自DevOps
in the UK and we had a really really
在英国，我们有一个非常非常
great meeting with hibernate team and
与休眠团队的愉快会议
the hibernate team is starting to look
冬眠团队开始寻找
at what a reactive JTA or reactive ORM
反应性JTA或反应性ORM
might look like and they're starting to
可能看起来像，他们开始
take a look at our two DB C as well
看看我们两个DB C
that'll probably be a bit further down
可能会进一步下降
the line bigger projects bigger plans
生产线更大的项目更大的计划
but everybody's sort of on board with
但是每个人都参与其中
this idea that we need this kind of
这个想法，我们需要这种
reactive data access to relational
反应性数据访问关系
databases so to finish it off we
数据库，以便完成它我们
finished up or sorry we we took a look
说完了还是对不起，我们来看了一下
at what the impediments were for people
对人们的阻碍是什么
to start doing react we identified the
为了开始做出反应，我们确定了
big three we had violetta up here
三巨头我们在这里紫罗兰
talking about the improvements we made -
谈论我们所做的改进-
to the core we talked about our socket
谈到我们的核心
as an opportunity to take back pressure
以此来减轻压力
across the wire and use a protocol
跨线并使用协议
that's more built for distributed
这是为分布式而构建的
systems than HTTP was and finally we
系统，而不是HTTP，最后我们
took a look at RTD BC for reactive
看看RTD BC的反应性
database access if you are interested
如果您有兴趣访问数据库
any of those three concepts violetta has
这三个概念中的任何一个violetta都有
a talk on Friday talking about the same
周五的一次讨论
stuff she did here including some
她在这里做的事情，包括一些
massive improvements she's done in
她所做的巨大改进
reactor Nettie I'm talking about our
Nettie反应堆我在说我们的
socket on Friday and Archie TBC later
星期五在套接字上，稍后有Archie TBC
this afternoon so thank you all
今天下午，谢谢大家
oh and I'm supposed to introduce up next
哦，我应该接下来介绍
Sebastian Toulouse to talk to us about
塞巴斯蒂安·图卢兹与我们交谈
Kotlin improvements in the Spring
春季Kotlin的改进
Framework Thanks
框架谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
okay so I wasn't at 12 okay okay stay my
好吧，所以我不是12点好吧，好吧，留下来
dear
亲
okay
好的
tests
测试
that's okay
没关系
okay you having any birds a mic yeah
好吧，你有一只鸟是麦克风吗
okay
好的
one two one two okay hi everybody I'm
一二一二好吧，大家好，我是
Sebastien doors I'm walking in pivoter
塞巴斯蒂安门，我正走在枢轴上
I'm a spring formal commuter and today
我是春季正式通勤者，今天
I'm going to talk about latest update of
我将谈论有关的最新更新
the Kirkland report in 2016
2016年的柯克兰报告
codeine window was released and the same
可待因窗口已发布，并且相同
day we added support for Kathleen
那天我们增加了对凯瑟琳的支持
instead of spring data Oh a few a few
而不是春季数据哦几
months later rather anon Scotland ESL
几个月后，苏格兰ESL
which has materialized recently in a
最近在
stable version in Gradle five a year
一年五个版本中的稳定版本
after we announced codeine officials
在我们宣布可待因官员之后
reports in spring for Mach five and on
春季报告五马赫及以后
druids unknowns its report for cutting
德鲁伊未知数削减报告
as well four hundred last year coup
以及去年的四百次政变
routines were announced as a stable
例行程序被宣布为稳定
feature of Kirkland 1.3 and a few days
Kirkland 1.3的功能和几天
ago at Google i/o Google announced that
之前在Google I / O，Google宣布
Android is now cut in first that means
现在首先切入Android，这意味着
that on the way dpi are now proposed by
现在dpi提出的方式是
default in cut in and then exposed later
默认为切入，稍后再显示
for photo Java developers so continued
对于照片Java开发人员，因此继续
eyes continues obviously a big part of
眼睛继续明显的很大一部分
this new curtain developers are coming
这个新的窗帘开发商来了
from the mobile world but we also see an
来自移动世界，但我们也看到了
increase of interest for codeine on
对可待因的兴趣增加
server side and I'm here to talk about
服务器端，我在这里谈论
that today but let's talk about why you
今天，但让我们谈谈你为什么
could be interested by Katrina I think
我想可能对卡特里娜飓风感兴趣
the first point is that it is a
第一点是，这是一个
pragmatic language but still elegant it
实用的语言，但仍然优雅
provides concrete tools like extension
提供扩展等具体工具
functions great interoperability with
具有强大的互操作性
Java a nice and concise not a library I
Java简洁明了而不是我的库
also think that the safety features of
也认为
Kathleen especially the new safety which
凯瑟琳特别是其中的新安全
is managed natively in the type system
在类型系统中本地管理
turn a kind of drawback of Java because
变成Java的一种缺点，因为
in in Java a new is a kind of thing we
在Java中，新事物是一种
want to avoid with optional and other
想要避免与可选和其他
thing like that into a powerful features
这样的东西变成了强大的功能
that allowed to deal with no safety at
使得在
compile time rather than dealing with
编译时间而不是处理
new pointer exception at runtime
运行时新的指针异常
I also think that code clean code
我也认为代码干净
provide better signal-to-noise ratio
提供更好的信噪比
than Java code and it make reactive
比Java代码更易反应
easier thanks to coroutines
由于协程更容易
so guru teens are cutting light wet
所以上师的青少年正在割湿
threads are going to write non-working
线程将无法正常工作
code in a more imperative way you can
您可以以更强制性的方式编写代码
see here the mapping between reactive
看到这里反应性之间的映射
and co-routines so basically for single
和协程，所以基本上是单身
values you will have an API that looked
值，您将拥有一个看起来像的API
like like imperative code with the
就像命令式代码
suspend keyword and flux will translate
暂停关键字，助焊剂将翻译
to flow so the flow type here is cut in
流动，所以这里的流动类型被切入
flow so they use the same type than the
流，因此它们使用的类型与
same name than the wrapper for reactive
与用于响应的包装器同名
streams implementation in Java in Java 9
Java 9中的Java流实现
but here we are really talking about
但是在这里我们真的在谈论
coding flow and that's the equivalent of
编码流程，相当于
flux incur it in words and in spring
助长词和春天
format 5.2 we provide built-in support
格式5.2我们提供内置支持
for co-routines
用于例程
by leveraging all the vector
通过利用所有向量
infrastructure so everything that
基础设施，使一切
Violetta and then I showed previously it
Violetta，然后我以前展示了它
will be CL circuits web flags
将是CL电路的网页标志
everything is used in the croute in
一切都在croute中使用
support that just another way to consume
支持另一种消费方式
the reactive infrastructure provided by
由...提供的反应性基础设施
spring like we also provide support for
就像我们也为春天提供支持
Erick Java in the design decision we
Erick Java在设计决策中我们
made whispering for mark 5 we really bet
悄悄地打了标记5我们真的打赌
on reactive streams for interval per
在无功流上每间隔
ability reason and here we are just
能力的原因，这就是
leveraging this interoperability to
利用这种互操作性
provide another way to consume reactive
提供消耗反应性的另一种方法
stack in a more imperative way I'm going
我要以更强制的方式堆叠
to show you a demo but before I have a
给你看演示，但是在我之前
little surprise for you thanks to the
多亏了
work of jean-baptiste ninja from the
吉恩-巴蒂斯特·忍者的作品
community and the walk of the spring to
社区和春天的漫步
team Springwood team especially Stefan
斯普林伍德队特别是斯蒂芬队
Leko as of today when you create a
到今天为止，当您创建一个
cutting project with Gradle build it
用Gradle切割项目来构建它
will use the Gradle cut in GSL instead
将改用GSL中的Gradle剪切
of the groovy ones and I'm going to show
时髦的，我将展示
you that concretely and with the demo so
具体说来就是和您一起演示的
we are going to create a new a new
我们将创建一个新的
reactive web application and we are
响应式Web应用程序，我们
going to do that thanks to the to start
由于要开始，所以要这样做
the spring the t'you integration that
春天，你的整合
there is an ID so I'm using status
有一个ID，所以我正在使用状态
window toyou I'm going to create a new
窗口给你，我要创建一个新的
project
项目
which is going to use Gradle obviously
这显然将使用Gradle
which was cut clean as a language okay
作为一种语言被砍干净了
we are going to customize the name then
我们将自定义名称
I'm choosing the latest and greatest
我正在选择最新和最伟大的
Millis tone of spring boot to the two
米利斯的春天引导到两个
and I'm just going to add the reactive
我将添加反应式
web dependency because one thing
网络依赖，因为一件事
important to understand is that all the
重要的是要了解
routines report is based on web flux
例行报告基于网络流量
webbing receipt does not report it okay
织带收据不报告好吗
okay so like I said as of today when you
好吧，就像我今天说的那样，当你
create a new when you create a new
创建新内容时创建新内容
Kirkland project with weather by default
柯克兰项目默认情况下具有天气
it generates a builder Gradle that kts
它生成一个kts的生成器Gradle
which is a Kirtland variant of Gradle
这是Gradle的Kirtland变体
the code look like bear is the same but
代码看起来像熊一样，但
you have more you can navigate
你还有更多可以浏览的
everything in statically type you have
静态类型的所有内容
documentation you have better
你有更好的文件
autocomplete so I think this variant of
自动完成，所以我认为
grader is interesting because weather is
平地机很有趣，因为天气
powerful but it also very it's very hard
功能强大，但也非常困难
so I when I use the groovy action I
所以当我使用常规动作时
mainly do copy and paste on internet and
主要在互联网上复制和粘贴
modify things we are here we are most
修改我们最在这里的东西
structured because everything is
结构化，因为一切都是
statically typed and I think that's a
静态类型，我认为这是一个
great combination now we are going to
伟大的组合，现在我们要
create a simple reactive application
创建一个简单的反应式应用程序
using Kotlin and web flux so I'm going
使用Kotlin和网络流量，所以我要
to let me add just the dependency so we
让我只添加依赖性，所以我们
are going to use bring data to the VCS
将使用将数据带到VCS
bring data to DBC is a way to consumer
将数据带到DBC是消费者的一种方式
to DBC that then has just presented in
到刚刚提交的DBC
spring world so we are going to add the
春天的世界，所以我们要添加
spring data to DBC we are going to use
将弹簧数据发送给DBC，我们将使用
PostgreSQL driver and we are going to
PostgreSQL驱动程序，我们将
add the dependency management because
添加依赖项管理，因为
since spring data to DBC is not final it
因为到DBC的春季数据不是最终数据
is not yet integrated in boot but later
尚未集成到引导中，但稍后
you will have starters and anything like
您将拥有入门和类似的东西
that
那
so I'm going to create my puzzle in
所以我要在里面创建我的难题
Kathleen so I'm going to create an
凯瑟琳，所以我要创建一个
so we are going to create a small API on
因此，我们将在
top of an article classes and let's take
文章顶部的课程，让我们来
some time to talk about the differences
有一段时间谈论差异
compared to compared to Java so we have
与Java相比，我们有
a class which is very concise because we
一个非常简洁的课程，因为我们
have this concise syntax that allowed to
具有这种简洁的语法，
declare at the same time the constructor
同时声明构造函数
parameters and the properties could mean
参数和属性可能意味着
push for immutable data structure so
推动不可变的数据结构
here we are using Val instead of Val to
在这里我们用Val代替Val
have immutable properties the data
具有不变的属性的数据
keywords allowed to generate
允许产生的关键字
automatically equals a squad and two
自动等于一个小队和两个
strings the types are three fixed and by
字符串的类型是三个固定的
default encoding the types are non
默认编码类型为非
usable that means that if you try to put
可用意味着如果您尝试放置
a new label value in title for example
例如标题中的新标签值
you will have another at compile time
您在编译时会有另一个
and if you want to specify a new label
以及是否要指定新标签
type you will use this kind of question
类型，您将使用此类问题
mark Aegean of the type to say this type
标记爱琴海的人说这种类型
is new label and newly balanced in in
是新标签，在
Kathleen means that it could have empty
凯瑟琳意味着它可能是空的
values so it's a kind of more powerful
值，这是一种更强大的功能
optional that you can also use for input
也可以用于输入的可选
parameters and other thing and you don't
参数和其他东西，你不会
have to pay the price in term of
必须付出代价
readability and performance to have a
易读性和性能
wrapper for that we are also using
我们也使用的包装器
another interesting feature which is
另一个有趣的功能是
optional parameter will default values
可选参数将为默认值
so instead of having to create another
因此不必创建另一个
overloaded version of the constructor
构造函数的重载版本
like in Java I am able to define
就像在Java中，我可以定义
optional parameter with default
可选参数，默认
parameters so if a new edge side I don't
参数，所以如果我没有新的边缘
specify Edline slag or edit add curtain
指定Edline炉渣或编辑添加幕布
we automatically use the default value
我们会自动使用默认值
that we provide here and in terms of
我们在这里提供的
readability I think that's interesting
可读性我认为这很有趣
now you see you see this to slag methods
现在你看到你看到这渣方法
which is in red obviously
显然是红色的
title is a string to slag is not a
标题是字符串，不是渣
method provided by by string type so we
字符串类型提供的方法，所以我们
are going to edit using extension
将使用扩展名进行编辑
functions so extension functions are a
功能，因此扩展功能是
mechanism that we use a lot in spring
春天大量使用的机制
from up to provide you
从上为您提供
a cutting specific API on top of
特定于切割的API
existing spring type but you can use it
现有的弹簧类型，但您可以使用它
for your own project and you should use
为您自己的项目，您应该使用
it instead of let's say abstract classes
它代替了抽象类
with static methods and here I'm adding
用静态方法，我在这里添加
a to slag metal that will transform a
将金属渣转化成
title with spaces and special characters
带空格和特殊字符的标题
to something that I can use and we are
到我可以使用的东西，我们
led onto fire to a string and then I can
着火了，然后我可以
use this kind of nice syntax so you
使用这种不错的语法，这样您
should not abuse of extension because
不应滥用扩展名，因为
you can do arrabal things but I think
你可以做些粗鲁的事情，但我认为
that's a pretty useful feature
这是一个非常有用的功能
especially given the fact that they are
特别是考虑到它们是
not magical ear it is in the same
不一样的耳朵
package so it is usable directly but if
包装，因此可以直接使用，但如果
my extension live in a different package
我的扩展程序位于其他程序包中
I have to import it explicitly like I
我必须像我一样明确导入
import static imports for example so
导入静态导入例如
it's not magical and dynamic everything
这不是魔术和动态的一切
is cut clean is a statically type as in
被切干净是静态类型
Java and even even more with the new
Java，甚至更多
safety feature now we are going to
安全功能，现在我们要
create an article repository using
使用创建一个文章库
spring data to the BC so article
春天数据到BC所以文章
repository ok like I said I have to
好的，就像我说过的
import extensions to make use of them ok
导入扩展以使用它们好
so this is an l2 DBC spring data - DBC
所以这是一个L2 DBC弹簧数据-DBC
based repository database parent is a
基于存储库数据库的父级是
functional API that is provided by
提供的功能性API
spring data to DBC in addition to the
将弹簧数据发送到DBC
regular repository model and we are
常规存储库模型，我们
going to use this kind of fluent API you
您将使用这种流利的API
can see that as a kind of web tie on for
可以将其视为一种网络连接
the database so you have this kind of
数据库，所以您有这种
same fluent API here I'm directly
同样的流利的API，我直接在这里
writing PostgreSQL code so I can
编写PostgreSQL代码，这样我就可以
leverage the native feature of poster
利用海报的本机功能
group
组
SQL awesome database if I want and
SQL很棒的数据库，如果我想和
spring that a 2d BCT take care of
2d BCT照顾的春天
transforming that into objects and you
把它变成物体，你
see the API return mono and flux I need
看到我需要的API返回单声道和通量
to specify that in code mean everything
指定代码意味着一切
is statically typed so here this is ins
是静态类型的，所以这里是ins
that the IDE display to me based on the
IDE会根据
content type in France so you see the
法国的内容类型，因此您会看到
API return mono and flux and we are
API返回单声道和通量，我们是
going
去
so yeah and season admitted when you use
所以是的，当你使用季节承认
second circuit you have to use this
第二个电路，你必须使用这个
reactive operators to do that I'm going
反应性操作员要做我要去的事
to add a controller also article
添加控制器也文章
controller so this is regular web first
控制器，因此这是常规网络优先
controller which is using flex and mono
使用flex和mono的控制器
based API and I'm just need to add just
基于API，我只需要添加
a bit of configuration because it is not
有点配置，因为它不是
yet supported on Josh
尚未在Josh上受支持
so we declare as database Kalyan bin
所以我们声明Kalyan bin为数据库
obviously when that will be supported in
显然，何时会支持
the final version you will not have to
最终版本，您将不必
do that and and that's it so I have
做到这一点，就是这样，我有
finished to implement my reactive
完成实施我的反应式
version now I'm going to turn that into
版本，现在我要把它变成
something which is more imperative with
更迫切的东西
coroutines but leveraging the very same
协程，但利用相同
underneath infrastructure so I'm going
在基础设施下面，所以我要去
to add the dependency for co-routines
添加对协同例程的依赖
okay so just that and then the strategy
好的，就是这样，然后是策略
that we have used is to provide routine
我们用来提供日常服务
reports on top of existing types using
报告使用以下现有类型
extension so you don't have to import a
扩展名，因此您不必导入
cou routine database beyond where
cou例程数据库超出何处
everything is wrapped we you can just
一切都包裹好了，我们可以
use this kind of extension so by
使用这种扩展名，因此
definition coroutines suspending
定义协程暂停
functions extensions are prefixed by a
功能扩展以a为前缀
way it was fixed by any weight and here
用任何重量固定的方式，在这里
you see I transform my method which were
你看我改变了我的方法
using reactive types like mono and flex
使用反应类型，例如mono和flex
to a method that is suspending and
挂起的方法
return just a plain new label of article
仅返回文章的新标签
I'm going to do the same job here so
我要在这里做同样的工作
instead of using flux I'm using flow
而不是使用流量，我使用流量
here I'm using a weight instead of them
这里我用的是重量而不是重量
and I make this a suspending same thing
我把这变成了悬念
here
这里
a weight i maximum is emitted suspending
重达最大的重量悬挂
same thing here and you will see that's
同样的事情，你会发现
not just about the return types the
不只是返回类型
style of programming will change so here
编程风格会改变，所以这里
instead of using reactive operators
而不是使用反应式运算符
I'm going to just use imperative code so
我将只使用命令式代码，因此
I just remove zero petals and I use the
我只去除零个花瓣，然后使用
same kind of code I would have used in
我本来会用的相同类型的代码
my imperative code except that see
我的命令性代码除外
underneath is based on directive stack
下面是基于指令栈
and let me be clear about two points
让我澄清两点
this deal with backpressure
处理背压
it deal with back pressure using
它使用
suspending function so you will see more
暂停功能，因此您将看到更多
detail in my talk tomorrow and also by
明天在我的演讲中也有详细介绍
default everything is second shot it's
默认一切都是第二枪
non blocking but second shot by default
非阻塞，但默认情况下为第二张
and you can do optional concurrency I
你可以做可选的并发我
won't show that today but believe me now
今天不会显示，但现在相信我
I'm going to change that so it is
我要改变它，所以
supported on spring data to DBC with
支持将弹簧数据发送到DBC
extensions here spring web flags
这里的扩展spring web flags
deal with it natively so I have nothing
本机处理，所以我一无所有
to do and I will transform that into
去做，我会把它变成
something which is much more imperative
更迫切的事情
so I will have written exactly the same
所以我写的完全一样
code in spring my spring MVC accept
春天的代码我的春天MVC接受
suspending functions now let's say I
现在让我暂停功能
want to do some kind of operation that
想做某种手术
you play latency for example calling a
您播放延迟，例如呼叫
remote web services so I'm going to
远程Web服务，所以我要
simulate that by this kind of suspending
通过这种悬浮来模拟
method but imagine that you are coding a
方法，但假设您正在编码
remote slow web service here it's
远程慢速Web服务在这里
returning a flow and flow provide
返回流量和流量提供
operators so like in Flex you have
像Flex这样的运算符
operators but here all these operators
运算符，但这里所有这些运算符
are extensions and the interesting thing
是扩展和有趣的事情
about map operator in coroutines
关于协程中的地图运算符
flow is that you can use you can coerce
流动就是可以使用就可以强迫
suspending function in them that means
暂停功能，这意味着
that you don't have to use flat map as
您不必将平面地图用作
soon as you have operation for latency
一旦有延迟操作
map is perfectly fine for that and last
地图是完美的，最后
thing and after that I will show you
事之后，我会告诉你
that that works for will hopefully if I
如果我能
want to use a server sent events
想要使用服务器发送的事件
endpoint something more in Moss trimming
在苔藓修剪中终结更多的东西
way and we use a flow instead of a flux
方式，我们使用流量而不是流量
and you see that inside my flow builder
你会在我的流程生成器中看到
this is just plain
这只是简单
imperative code I'm just
我只是命令式代码
using a while loop that will emit so
使用while循环将发出
this is push bass and flow so you emit a
这是推低音和流，所以你发出一个
new object that is button potentially
可能是按钮的新对象
coming from a suspending function and I
来自暂停功能，我
simulate some kind of latency with with
用来模拟某种延迟
that so if I run the application now I
因此，如果我现在运行该应用程序，
think I've forgotten something
以为我忘记了什么
yeah so I just use rainbow King here
是的，所以我在这里用彩虹之王
this is the coup routines we are showing
这是我们展示的政变常规
off block but conceptually this is the
封闭，但从概念上讲这是
same because suspending function need to
相同，因为挂起功能需要
be call from another suspending function
被另一个挂起函数调用
so I start my application and then if I
所以我开始我的申请，然后如果我
request my route endpoint you see that
请求我的路线终点，您会看到
it returned my my object that I have put
它返回了我放的我的对象
in the initializer and if I want to
在初始化器中，如果我想
stream data you see that my associate
流数据，您看到我的同事
point works like if I would have used
点的工作就像我会使用
flex and everything support suspending
flex和一切都支持暂停
function so it's really reactive
功能，所以真的很反应
programming but with an imperative
编程，但势在必行
programming model in terms of scope we
就范围而言，编程模型
support cool routines for web flags both
同时支持酷炫的网络标志例程
for the annotated controller programming
用于带注释的控制器编程
model and for the web flex functional
模型和Web Flex功能
variants we have cout routines
我们有cout例程的变体
extensions for web clients also a
网络客户端扩展也
speaker circuits report on spring with
扬声器电路报告弹簧
Atmos H mapping and a circuit a circuit
Atmos H映射和电路
requester provide a coup routines API
请求者提供妙招例程API
and on spring that aside we provide it
而在春天，我们提供它
on functional API slay like F 2d BC
像F 2d BC一样使用功能性API
database clients and we provide as well
数据库客户端，我们也提供
extensions for template or operation
模板或操作的扩展
based API from spring that a MongoDB
从春天开始基于MongoDB的API
Kisan run Redis reports let me finish by
Kisan运行Redis报告让我结束
ESL's so DSL are a way to write ap is in
ESL的DSL是写ap的一种方式
a kind of decorative way you can
一种可以装饰的方式
register in Java but it will look like
在Java中注册，但看起来像
not awesome and at least
不很棒，至少
Java does not provide you specific tools
Java没有为您提供特定工具
to help you to write at yourself why
帮你写自己的理由
Kathleen provide you really dedicated
凯瑟琳为您提供真正的专注
feature for that so this is the routed
为此的功能，这是路由
yourself that we have provided since
我们提供的您自己
spring for Mach 5 dot Oh
5马赫的弹簧哦
and the new feature in spring for Mach
以及Mach春季的新功能
5.2 is that we provide that as well for
5.2是我们也为
spring MVC so you can never edge
Spring MVC，让您永无止境
like it was announced previously by
就像之前由
again you can leverage spring MVC Tomcat
再次，您可以利用spring MVC Tomcat
and just use this kind of nice DSL where
并使用这种不错的DSL
you can combine requests by decades
您可以按数十年合并请求
provides some kind of dynamic code to
提供某种动态代码来
generic routes and that's I think that's
通用路线，那是我认为的
a pretty good fit with with Kathleen I
非常适合Kathleen I
would like her to finish by your
希望她在你的帮助下完成
projects that came to me last year here
去年来我这里的项目
at spring IO thinking about that it's
在春季IO想到的是
tofu so curfew as it is an experimental
宵禁是如此的实验性豆腐
explicit configuration model for spring
弹簧的显式配置模型
butchers in the question DSL this is not
屠夫在问题DSL这不是
production ready this is experimental
准备生产，这是实验性的
this is incubating okay I don't use that
这正在孵化，好吧，我不使用它
in production but I would like to
在生产中，但我想
present it because after the beans and
提出它，因为在豆类和
the route or DSL I think this is a very
路由或DSL我认为这是一个非常
good use case for the acetylcholine it
乙酰胆碱的好用例吗
just to configure spring boot in an
只是在配置弹簧启动
explicit way so the new features of the
明确的方式，以便
re0 that one minestrone I have published
re0我发布的一个蔬菜通心粉汤
yesterday is that is report both web
昨天是报告两个网站
blogs and web MVC and it took like that
博客和网络MVC，就像那样
so basically you configure spring boot
所以基本上你配置Spring Boot
with a programmatic API you define if
使用程序化API定义是否
that's a standalone a servlet based on a
这是一个独立的基于
reactive a web application and you can
反应一个Web应用程序，您可以
you can configure everything with
您可以使用
autocomplete directly from your IDE so
直接从您的IDE自动完成
you can configure the log level you can
您可以配置日志级别
use obviously dynamic stuff coming from
使用明显来自动态的东西
the environment everything is not
环境不是一切
everything is dynamic it's just plain
一切都是动态的，这很简单
cutting code so like in the port
像在港口一样切割代码
definition you can use dynamic if or for
您可以使用动态的if或for定义
statements you it leverage the bins and
声明您利用垃圾箱和
the root or DSL and provide an explicit
根或DSL并提供明确的
configuration model so basically it
配置模型，基本上
leverage all the Springwood
利用所有的Springwood
configuration stuff without the
没有配置的东西
conditional annotation so basically you
有条件的注释，所以基本上你
are in charge to declaring that you want
负责宣布您要
string and Jack's rejection converters
串和杰克的拒绝转换器
in that order and that projects on
以此顺序，并在
converter you want to use the pretty
您想使用漂亮的转换器
print and the interesting thing is that
打印，有趣的是
since you only specify what you need it
因为您只指定需要的内容
will be more efficient because it just
会更有效率，因为它只是
you just will get what you need
您将得到所需的东西
and it will yeah once you bless me my
一旦你祝福我我的
wrists are faster because you you you
手腕更快，因为你
yeah and it does not new features does
是的，它没有新功能
not pop up because you add a dependency
因为您添加了依赖项而没有弹出
everything is explicit you are in
一切都是明确的，你在
control less surprised so I think that's
控制不那么惊讶，所以我认为
an interesting programming model if you
一个有趣的编程模型，如果您
are interested go to the spring foo
有兴趣去春季foo
repository where this projecting few
这个投影的地方很少
baits add the star of the project
诱饵成为项目的明星
contribute we have people from the
贡献我们有来自
community that are involved for example
例如涉及的社区
somebody in this room from the community
社区里有人在这个房间里
is walking on a spring security cart
在弹簧安全车上行走
India cell that will be integrated in in
印度单元将被整合到
Kofu and maybe later in spring security
甲府，也许稍后在春季安全
so feel free to to come and contribute I
所以随时来贡献我
will give more information tomorrow in
明天将提供更多信息
the days I am in a dedicated talk with
我与之专门交谈的日子
tofu and co-routines live coding thanks
豆腐和例程进行实时编码，谢谢
a lot
很多
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]